

ABOUT

I am a full-stack web developer who is inspired to bridge my dynamic programming skills with my healthcare experience.
I strive to serve local organizations with creative development solutions that stem from an eclectic and contemplative background.

CONTACT

pdpadian@gmail.com

(908)-821-5003

www.paulpadian.com

www.linkedin.com/in/paul-padian

SKILLS

Problem Solving
Adaptability
Collaboration
Time Management
Critical Thinking
Team-Oriented

TECH STACK

React VUE Next.js MongoDB Psql Javascript CSS HTML

PAUL PADIAN

Full Stack Software Engineer

PROJECTS

Minesweeper

 Created a Vanilla JS minesweeper application to explore game logic and javascript data structures

Crossfit Verve Refactor

- Refactored a local business's website to incentivize created content and provide clients with a simplified user experience.
- Provided business owners with approachable tools for user maintenance and content creation.

DevSpot

- Created a full stack application that allows developers to grow together through project collaboration.
- Worked in a team setting using git and version control.

EXPERIENCE

General Assembly

Software Engineering Immersive | 2020 - Present (Remote)

 Three-month, 500-hour full-time and full-stack program conducted in a remote setting, providing experience with the latest front and back-end programming languages, tools and methodologies.

Haven House

Medical Tech | 2016 - 2018 (Los Angeles, CA)

- Implemented systems and training for facility compliance with Icaho and HIPAA standards.
- Audited and maintained database of electronic medical records for HIPAA compliance.

EDUCATION

General Assembly

Software Engineering Immersive | 2020 - Present (Remote)

• Developed a portfolio of individually and collaboratively focused projects.

Community College of Denver

Registered Nursing | 2018 - 2020 (Remote)

Full time study of nursing fundamentals